(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
The hospital?
I just got her admitted.
And I have to pick up things for Momo.
Then come to the Gangnam Hotel.
Let's get breakfast.
Don't you have a morning flight?
When did you get vertigo?
Not long ago.
How did you end up with Ju Shin?
Director Shin gave me a ride after dinner.
I suddenly got so dizzy
that I just sank to the ground.
Don't get too close to Ju Shin.
Keep him at arm's length.
Why?
You saw what happened with Momo.
The guy's pretty heartless
when it comes to women.
I thought you were asking me to breakfast
because you were worried...
about Momo.
(Red Bean Rice Cakes)
I hope it doesn't rain in Jeju.
Let's see...
Your dad finally got to take his staff
to Jeju.
Man, I could really go for
some red bean rice cakes.
(Yong Joong)
We had just gotten to the hotel in Jeju
and were unpacking...
when we heard
the father of the head of marketing...
had passed away.
Did he have a chronic condition?
No. Just high blood pressure.
High blood pressure is chronic.
Good to see you both. It's been a while.
(Red Bean Rice Cakes)
Are you and Ba Ra dating?
We're not quite at that stage yet.
I'm thinking of skipping the dating
and going straight to marriage.
I already proposed.
What were you thinking?
You just called off your wedding.
What does time have to do with it?
You can fall for someone in an instant...
and fall out of love just as quickly.
So, what did Ba Ra say?
It's really coming down.
You need to be less jumpy.
I can't come running every time.
Thank you.
You should go now.
I told you not to thank me.
Are you sulking?
Why would I sulk at you?
What do you mean, "why"?
I've decided to marry you.
I just feel bad that
you're the second person I've asked.
Please, don't even think about it.
I can think whatever I want.
If you keep this up,
I can't be comfortable around you.
Do you have any ramyeon?
Isn't that the popular line these days?
"Want to stay for ramyeon?"
Did you see that on TV?
I heard the nurses talking about it.
Didn't you eat dinner?
No.
Gosh, how embarrassing.
What's embarrassing?
You're not exactly the timid type.
Just stay in the car.
Don't you have an umbrella in the trunk?
I don't know. Can't be bothered.
Please remove your card.
I didn't even know this place existed.
You never noticed it driving by?
I'm usually asleep in the car.
You sound like an old man.
I like getting the senior treatment.
I'll do it for you.
Do you eat bean sprouts?
I'm not a big fan of toppings.
Not even an egg?
(Regular Noodles)
These days, it's not "ramyeon."
It's "Want to come up and watch a show?"
Or, "Want to come up and see my cat?"
That's what they say now.
Oh, Pickles.
James is looking after him for me.
He was really heartbroken
after Oiji crossed the rainbow bridge.
So he likes seeing him from time to time.
Everything dies.
It's a bit of an exaggeration,
but I deal with it almost every day.
There's no point in getting attached.
- So that means...
- Don't lecture me.
The same goes for you.
Do you always have to have the last word?
It's so you get sick of it.
Let's go to James's after we eat.
- Don't you want to see Pickles?
- It's almost 10 p.m.
James doesn't go to bed
until after midnight.
He has insomnia.
Besides,
I'm curious about the furball myself.
That's a good thing.
You must be cold.
What if you catch a cold?
Then you can come make me
some bean sprout soup.
I'm serious.
I'll make it for you.
Does it taste okay?
It's delicious.
You handle hot food better
than I expected.
A surprising number of male reporters
can't handle hot food.
Ramyeon's no good when it gets cold.
Our food tastes are compatible too.
How about some ice cream for dessert?
I saw they had those
squeeze-up ones, right?
Might as well let you
treat me to dessert, too.
Okay.
What's the coffee-flavored one like?
It tastes like sweet coffee.
Just save me a bite.
I'm already soaked.
How am I supposed to eat two of these?
I'll finish it if you don't.
But I thought you liked being treated.
That's not the kind of treatment
I had in mind.
You're the one
who's going to catch a cold.
You're not a germaphobe?
It won't kill me.
Besides,
it's good to share beneficial bacteria.
Hey, James, it's me.
You picked up right away.
Can I swing by for a bit?
Yes.
I'm not going. It's an imposition.
What's he going to think
if we show up together this late?
He'll probably think we're dating.
I don't need to see Pickles.
But I want to see him.
He's probably going to think
you abandoned him.
It's a she.
She's a female?
Yes.
That's a crude way to put it.
Should I call her "young girl"
or "young lady"?
Is "female dog" any better?
Actually,
calling yourself a pet's "mom" or "dad"
is a bit much.
True.
People raise dogs instead of having kids.
I'd be perfectly happy
just living with Pickles.
Do you have any ginger tea or anything?
No.
I do at my place.
I just sneezed because of the change
in temperature.
When it rains,
don't draw the curtains and hide in fear.
Just watch it.
If you watch, you'll see it's not scary.
It's actually refreshing.
When I'm faced with hardship,
I just say,
"Bring it on. I'll meet it head-on."
I don't run from it.
That's a different issue.
It might be a different issue,
but that's the attitude I live with.
To live...
Want to share some beneficial microbes?
They're good for your immune system.
Please be serious.
I am being serious.
You really don't see me as a man?
I do. But that's a different issue.
"A different issue," miss.
I've grown to like you.
I never expected it.
So this is all I am to Yong Joong.
With no romantic spark.
I'll wait.
You can't force feelings.
Just not for too long.
Don't let me celebrate my 60th birthday
as a lonely bachelor.
These days,
people don't even celebrate turning 70.
She shot me down.
I saw it coming.
You two aren't like siblings, are you?
If she really saw you as a man,
she would've told you right away.
She probably thought
it was better left unsaid.
Because it's just too absurd.
What about today?
The rain was coming down so hard.
And she mentioned
that she was scared of it.
We also stopped by your brother's place
to see Pickles.
Oh, my goodness! Come on in.
I'm sorry to impose, but I tagged along.
Nonsense! You're more than welcome!
Pickles.
What brings you two busy people here?
Have you two had dinner?
I thought her heart would be
trembling in fear, so I went to see her.
And she ended up buying me ramyeon.
What's wrong with her heart?
He's kidding.
He knows I'm afraid of thunderstorms,
so he stopped by since he was nearby.
I guess she was a dog in a past life.
What about you?
- What was your past life...
- A deity.
Ju as in "master," Shin as in "spirit."
Let him dream.
- Should I make some fried rice?
- I've had enough carbs for one day.
- I'll grill some meat for you.
- We were just stopping by.
They say dogs take after their owners,
so we were worried she'd be scared.
Oh, she was.
Does Yong Joong stop by often?
He checks in on me whenever he can.
He treats me like an old man,
saying he doesn't age.
He should be good to his older brother.
I just wish he'd meet someone nice.
But there's a proper order to things.
- You have to get married first.
- Why don't you set me up with someone?
You're always around female celebs...
It's not like the young, beautiful celebs
are throwing themselves at me.
And I can't just go and hit on them.
They have to be young and beautiful,
but they have to have beautiful minds too.
Exactly.
When is Yong Joong coming to Jeju?
The day after tomorrow.
I have a villa in Jeju.
You should go and relax for a bit.
It's a shame for it to just sit empty.
Maybe with me someday?
Ba Ra isn't right for you.
And you're not the right man for Ba Ra.
Think about this carefully.
You don't have to explain why.
Don't lead her on.
She's worked hard to rebuild her life.
- She's the one who got to me.
- And I suppose Momo led you?
That is different.
A crush is a crush.
It's all the same thing.
You only think about yourself.
Have I ever done anything to upset you?
If you were to marry our nurse, Lee Shim,
I would go along with it.
Not because I don't value our friendship,
but because that's how much
I'd trust and respect your judgment.
Both you and Ba Ra are important to me.
You're like a brother to me,
and Ba Ra is like a sister.
We're surprisingly compatible.
- That's just your opinion.
- This wasn't an impulsive decision.
I have a really strong feeling about this.
You're the only one feeling it.
Geum Ba Ra is falling for me, too.
Little by little.
Some love is like a rising tide,
but this is like a gentle rain...
that seeps in slowly.
But you're always a rising tide.
And the tide always goes back out.
This time it's really different.
It seems just as impulsive to me.
I'm asking you, seriously,
but don't push her into this.
All right, then let me ask you,
just to be sure.
Do you have any
romantic feelings for Ba Ra?
Think about it carefully.
We're really just like brother and sister,
just not by blood.
All right, then.
Goodness.
Going to bed already?
There's nothing else to do now.
(Missed calls)
(Paul)
Why did you quit the newspaper?
How did you know that?
Your articles stopped,
so I got curious and looked into it.
And I heard you quit.
I'm on a break, helping a close friend.
A close friend?
Momo?
Yes.
Then you must have heard.
I asked Momo...
for a picture of my daughter,
but she said she didn't have any.
You met with her?
Does that make any sense?
It's possible she doesn't.
She might have deleted them
to try to forget.
If you have a picture of my daughter...
You don't have any?
What about a recent one?
We were both busy,
so we didn't see each other often.
So you weren't that close?
So you had a falling out.
Honestly, it still doesn't feel real.
Exactly. Me neither.
How old was she here?
Fourth grade.
- My Jin Ju?
- Yes.
Why were you so tiny, Reporter Geum?
For a fourth grader?
It's not like you were a baby.
Do you really think my Jin Ju is dead?
Considering her body
still hasn't turned up,
I just couldn't believe it,
no matter how hard I tried,
so I went to see a shaman.
She said she was not dead...
and that she was still alive.
I stayed up for two days straight.
I was just so miserable.
I may be a pathetic father,
but I'm still her father.
The only thing keeping me going
was the thought of finding her.
But she thinks she can hide
just because she finds me useless?
The police have closed the investigation.
They're in on it together. Her and Momo.
She's definitely hiding her somewhere.
I heard celebrities own multiple houses.
Do you know where her second home is?
I wouldn't know about that.
Even if you knew,
you wouldn't tell me anyway.
I only heard she has a condo in Jeju,
but I've never been there.
How was...
Momo's relationship with my daughter?
It was...
nothing special.
If she were dead,
why doesn't she appear in my dreams?
Spirits are supposed to visit you
if they're dead.
Then what about the memorial?
It went smoothly.
It was all for nothing then.
Didn't he just dump Momo for Ba Ra?
It's no contest.
I look like such an old man.
James.
You bought this at the airport,
didn't you?
I heard Ju Shin and Ba Ra stopped by.
Ju Shin is totally into Ba Ra.
I'm a pro at reading people,
and I'm sure about this.
What about Ba Ra?
She was just her usual self.
That guy's so unpredictable.
You're not wrong.
Could I give Momo the same treatment
you gave me, Director Shin?
Looks easy, doesn't it?
Explain it to me in detail.
You don't even know if the problem's
in her left or right ear,
or if it's an issue
with the horizontal semicircular canal,
or an abnormality in
the posterior semicircular canal.
If you do it wrong, the crystals could
end up in multiple canals.
And then it gets really complicated.
They say,
"A little knowledge is a dangerous thing."
If you were with me,
you'd never have to worry
about vertigo again.
Reporter Geum's going to end up
marrying the Nua hospital's director.
If I were her, why would I say no?
Right now, she probably feels insecure,
so she can't just say yes right away.
Ba Ra's not a gold digger like that.
It's not being a gold digger.
It's becoming Cinderella.
It's not like he was married.
Was that engagement to Momo a big deal?
Depending on how you look at it,
it's practically a badge of honor.
Beating out a top star like Momo.
Momo would be going crazy with jealousy.
That's probably the main reason
Reporter Geum is hesitating, too.
But still.
They say if you chop at a tree enough,
it's bound to fall.
And knowing Director Shin's personality,
he'd probably chop at it 100 times.
Right?
I can finally breathe.
How could Yong Joong not even
send a text to see if I'm okay?
The shaman said that she wasn't dead?
Yes.
He seems to suspect you of hiding her.
That's crazy.
So what happened?
I heard he asked you for a picture, too.
- Did you give him one?
- An old one I had.
Let me see. Which one did you give him?
I didn't notice it when I first met him,
but his eyes...
are creepy.
He's my enemy, not my father.
What gives him the right?
Search all you want.
Kim Gwang Cheol can run, but I can fly.
That jerk, Shin Ju Shin.
If he'd just fixed this that day,
I wouldn't be going through all this.
The hospital can't really do
much for you, right?
- Right.
- They just taught you some exercises.
Right.
I asked Ba Ra to marry me.
When?
So, what did she say?
She said no.
How could you...
Are you out of your mind?
Watch your mouth.
How long has it been
since our breakup article?
And her, of all people?
- Geum Ba Ra is a better choice.
- How is she better?
Stop talking nonsense out of spite.
Should I just pull my hair back
and expose that I'm Kim Jin Ju?
- Go ahead.
- What do you think would happen then?
Is that a threat?
Your biological father, Kim Gwang Cheol,
would be the first one to come running.
And what do you think the world would say?
He's still your biological father,
after all.
For a daughter to do such a thing.
In this situation, it's a win-win for us.
What's in it for me?
What does that make me?
This is so humiliating.
People will forget soon enough.
You just have to find someone better.
Just like that?
You're Momo, after all.
In life, if you try hard enough,
you can pretty much get what you want.
Why Geum Ba Ra of all people?
I know Geum Ba Ra better than you do.
You're getting way ahead of yourself.
Ba Ra would never...
Don't jinx it. Put in a good word for me.
Think about all I've done for you.
I turned Cinderella Kim Jin Ju
into the superstar Momo.
I sometimes miss
my old body and my old face.
You want me to change your face back
to look like Kim Jin Ju?
I can get it pretty close.
- You're here.
- Yes.
Should I ask him
about that shaman's house?
No, he might get suspicious
if I bring it up.
Have you been well, Mr. Kim?
It's Geum Ba Ra.
I'm afraid all I have to offer
is green tea.
Your paintings always make me
feel so warm.
Pick one out.
I'd rather work hard
and earn the money to buy one.
I can tell you genuinely love my work.
That's why I want to give you one.
Then let's do a gift exchange later.
I was traveling, starting from Namhae,
and an artist friend
in Boryeong made me stay,
so I was there for two days.
- The artist, Hong Seon Hui.
- I know her.
She's single, just like you.
Her painting style is very dynamic.
Yes, and she's as strong and free-spirited
as her art.
The youngest daughter
of the Seven Princesses' House.
Because her parents were hoping for a son?
Yes.
Next August...
That's plenty of time to prepare, right?
I might have to go to Germany.
Do you have an exhibition?
In Korea, he'd be my older cousin brother
on my father's side.
He always really looked out for me.
But...
he was diagnosed with cancer.
- Oh, no.
- He's started chemo,
but I feel like I need to go see him.
Of course.
We'll send a special invitation to you.
Is Momo...
doing well?
Yes.
Tell her I said hi.
I will.
I guess you don't come
to Seoul very often.
Every once in a while...
That must be our curator.
The local market was open,
so I did some browsing
and bought a few things.
And I stopped by Jangichu
for these coffee beans.
You shouldn't have.
Perfect timing.
He was just saying he ran out of coffee.
Get that troublesome Ba Ra out of the way
by giving her to Shin Ju Shin?
As they say, "The ends justify the means."
If I want Ha Yong Joong,
it might be better if Ba Ra is married.
How can I stand by and watch her become
the Nua Foundation chairman's wife?
Shin Ju Shin... Ha Yong Joong...
Ha Yong Joong is so much more personable
and manly.
What if my brain were in Ba Ra's body?
Ba Ra...
She's only had eyes for Ha Yong Joong,
so she won't open up to someone else.
And believe it or not,
she's got her pride.
Your mother has been managing
the artists so well,
so I think the exhibition
will go off without a hitch.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why did I have to hear it
from Director Shin?
There's no reason for you to refuse.
I never even considered it.
I made myself perfectly clear,
so I didn't need to bring it up.
But he seemed so sure of himself.
You know me.
Don't you?
It's not exactly normal for Director Shin
to ask you to marry him, is it?
Deep down, are you tempted?
- You never know with people's hearts.
- Time will tell.
So it's Ha Yong Joong and no one else?
We need to find a new curator, fast.
Jeong Ah is moving to the US.
Her husband got transferred
to the LA branch.
Maybe I should just close the gallery.
It's overwhelming.
You're on leave anyway.
Just have fun doing whatever you want,
and then go back to your job
at the newspaper.
I'll keep you on the payroll
for a few more months.
You're coming with us to Singapore
next month, right?
Singapore? What for?
Haven't you heard?
"A Maiden's Prayer"
has become a massive sleeper hit.
For a fan meeting.
That's great.
But I don't really have to go, do I?
But Singapore is so nice.
They have great food too.
(Yong Joong)
When are you getting here?
Waiting for you in an empty house.
Even if you're not interested,
when someone confesses
their feelings like that,
I bet you could start to develop them.
It wasn't exactly a confession.
Frankly, I don't get Director Shin either.
You know Ju Shin.
He's not the type to give up easily.
No.
He's not the type
to get needlessly obsessed.
Because of that pride of his.
I just have to meet him
and make myself clear again.
What do you think?
You're the one who said
I should find a good man, right?
As a doctor, he's perfect,
but Ju Shin is
not exactly marriage material.
He's not the type
to go all-in for a woman.
He admits it himself.
And you?
You're the type who would go all-in
for a woman?
How can anyone be perfect
and good at everything?
- Are you making excuses for him?
- It's not an excuse, it's the truth.
Now that you've gotten an offer like that,
are you swayed?
Where did your pride go, Geum Ba Ra?
That was just pride born from insecurity.
It's from fighting and winning
your battles,
the self-respect from doing your best.
You're the one who has lived that way.
Though you do fall apart
when it comes to Momo.
What are you talking about?
So are you saying you're against it?
I'm worried you'll end up like Momo.
Is that the only reason?
Ju Shin's an old friend,
but honestly, I'm worried about you.
What am I, a child?
Geum Ba Ra needs to be happy from now on.
And she deserves every bit of it.
- How?
- By finding a much better guy.
Don't worry.
He's just the son of the chairman
I'm indebted to.
Just the director.
Got any drinks?
I had a few bottles of wine,
but I gave them as gifts to some writers.
We can just order some.
Or should we go out?
Why didn't you visit Momo in the hospital?
I'm sure you wanted to.
Is she okay now?
She's been discharged.
There wasn't much the hospital
could do for her anyway.
You want the honest truth?
It didn't even cross my mind.
I completely forgot.
You're lying.
I'm serious.
I only remembered when you mentioned it.
Were you that busy?
It seems Ju Shin rushed to the karaoke bar
that day, thinking it was you.
I'm a guy too, but it is what it is.
You really can't trust people's feelings.
But some feelings never change.
Like mine.
Like you.
I wouldn't know about that.
What about the marketing head's funeral?
It went as well as it could.
It must've been so devastating.
It means while we're alive,
we really have to live without regrets.
We have to do our best
for the people by our side...
and love them.
You, of course...
I said you were my number one, right?
You'll marry who's before number one.
Why is this soju
going down so smoothly today?
It's giving me a perfect buzz.
Look at you changing the subject.
I'm not changing the subject.
That hurt!
And here I thought I was the only one
who found you pretty.
But since it was you,
you didn't fall for it.
Ju Shin would make a move on any woman
he had a connection to.
Classmates from med school,
underclassmen, you name it.
You get tons of calls
from matchmakers too, don't you?
And I hear plenty of women
hit on you at bars and places.
When did I ever tell you that?
James did.
I have to be the one who's interested.
Most guys are like that.
So that means I have absolutely no chance.
According to Ju Shin,
you two are a good match.
We can hold a conversation, I guess.
That's about it.
From now on, only talk to me.
You can only ramble on in front of me.
I guess I'll ramble with you
and talk politely with Director Shin.
What's gotten into you?
What about you?
What's wrong with me?
You know I'm always on your side,
no matter what.
Spare me the lip service.
I mean it.
If it weren't for his history with Momo,
I might've actually considered
giving the Director a chance.
So you are attracted to him.
You're saying you're attracted to him.
It's scary how
you can get attached to people.
You've gotten attached?
He was intimidating, and it was awkward.
But now, I somehow feel as comfortable
with him as I do with you.
Some paths aren't meant to be taken.
It will only end in heartbreak,
just like with Momo.
Momo's the one who ended it.
And so he hits her?
You never hit a woman. Ever.
There's absolutely no excuse.
You must have been so heartbroken,
hearing how he hit her.
If he'd done that to you,
I would've half-killed Ju Shin.
You have me,
so you can do whatever you want...
and live your life
with your head held high.
My whole life?
Are you going to find me a good man
and marry me off?
Honestly, that's not going to be easy.
You know how people say
men are all animals?
There's not a single decent guy
I know to recommend.
You're a different breed from most guys.
So am I a 90...
out of 100.
Straight A's.
In every way.
You won't find another angel like me.
You have no idea.
I can be pretty wicked
in my head sometimes.
It's okay if you get wicked.
And I have pointless thoughts, too.
What kind of pointless thoughts?
Guys probably don't daydream like this.
They say people in Korea run
on the power of rice,
but I've always run
on the power of my fantasies.
Isn't that just dreaming, not fantasizing?
A plan. An ambition.
If you could turn my fantasy
into reality for me,
that would be wonderful.
Tell me.
Anything.
What is it?
Have you heard of
"What day? Monday, birthday?"
No, but I feel like I should.
If you do, you're an old man.
Age-wise, I guess I am.
Your face is nothing like an old man's.
I'll tell you after I finish my drink
and lose my filter.
I think I know.
You wanted to be a dancer, not a reporter.
You said you only backup danced
at karaoke bars.
I think I've had the perfect amount
to drink today.
You should go.
I don't want to.
I like this vibe. It's so comfortable.
I want to keep talking.
I love you.
Me too.
Don't copy me.
After today, don't say
"I love you" anymore.
I'll be the only one to say it.
- Yong Joong.
- Yes?
School clubs...
You only took
the high school equivalency exam, right?
- Are you talking about college clubs?
- Yes. I was in the dance club.
I've got some moves.
If it wasn't for Momo's vertigo that day,
I would've gotten to see
my baby's dance moves.
Don't call me "baby" today.
Here you go, Princess.
The reason that
I joined the dance club was...
You know how in foreign movies,
- brides do a father-daughter dance.
- Yes.
But no matter how many times I marry,
I won't have a dad to dance with.
But I still wanted to learn how.
I guess I felt like something was missing.
If he's even alive out there,
or if he's already passed on.
Tonight, don't think of me
as your brother.
Think of me as your dad.
But I can't dance.
Just feel the rhythm.
I love you, Yong Joong.
I love you.
Where are you headed?
The tech show. Going to the conference?
Yes. The one in Las Vegas?
(Text Message)
(Momo: Hello.
Sorry, I've had my phone turned off.)
Hello.
Sorry, I've had my phone turned off.
(Text Message)
Are you free to talk?
(Paul)
Hello?
What? Was he some Korean guy?
He has a nice voice, though.
Hello?
It's been a while.
Yes.
I read that Kim Jin Ju went missing,
and I thought about calling you...
Who is this? How does he know me?
We should get a meal sometime
when you're free.
Sure. I'm free these days.
Send me a few dates that work for you,
and I'll pick a place and text you.
How about tomorrow?
I wonder who he is...
Good, I'm not late.
I hit traffic right as I was getting here.
Hello.
- Yes.
- Is a table by the window okay?
No way... It's him?
Are you Kim Young Jun, by any chance?
What about the name Kim Jin Ju?
It's just what I was named,
and what I've always been called.
- I'll have the same.
- Okay.
So how does he know Momo?
I've been worried about you.
You seem better than I thought.
I'm not really.
I think the shock from everything
that happened was too much,
making my memory spotty.
My doctor says it's temporary amnesia...
Really?
Yes.
So you don't remember me either?
Not exactly.
So tell me already.
You called me after your mom
told you the whole story.
I did?
We had met before that at an exhibition.
You were with Geum Ba Ra, the reporter.
What whole story?
What story are you talking about?
It's just...
It's not important, so don't worry
about it if you can't remember.
No, please tell me.
Please, I'm asking.
My memories are all jumbled up,
and I can't sleep well.
Yes, Mr. Ha.
Does Pickles have a regular vet?
- Why?
- He had diarrhea a few times yesterday,
and now he won't eat and is lethargic.
Thank you.
Just switch his food
and he should be fine.
- Okay.
- Come on, let's go.
First off, congratulations.
I heard from Yong Joong.
It's definitely something to celebrate.
I know Director Shin better than anyone.
And I'm the one
who introduced him to Momo.
But it just wasn't meant to be.
Just accept your good fortune.
You'll regret it if you let him go.
Think of it as a blessing from the sky.
Even if you had unlucky parents,
you can be lucky in marriage.
And if you lack both, the deity will
bless you with good children, right?
I was lucky to have
good adoptive parents...
- I...
- What a nice day.
Oh my, what breed is that?
- I'll tell you later.
- I'll just order something.
- Okay.
- Alright.
- What breed is your dog?
- He's a White Terrier.
He looks familiar.
She's a dog model, Agati.
- No wonder. She's so beautiful.
- You can just tell, can't you?
Yes, I knew she looked like a model.
Oh my, she's so gorgeous.
Hi there.
(International Flights)
(Las Vegas, Landed)
You already spent so much
time on me today.
I will next time
when my hands aren't so cold.
Why are your hands cold? Are you cold?
I just have that type of body.
My body gets cold if I don't eat beef.
Did you have a pleasant flight?
I did, thank you.
The doors are closing.
Now that you mention it,
I vaguely remember...
So, that means I have an older sister...
So that's CEO Hyun's dirty little secret?
Jin Ju, your hair is so lovely and thick.
Mom.
She ran a DNA test.
To see if, by any chance,
I was her daughter.
So she faked her death and went to him
pretending to be Momo.
I wonder if my birth mother
ever thinks about me.
She must, if she's even human.
Why did she have to fall
for a guy like that?
If she had a kid,
she should've taken responsibility.
You know the saying.
"Live together, die together."
On top of that,
to abandon your own flesh and blood...
Ms. Ba Ra is here.
(Korean beef)
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
(Message from Geum Ba Ra)
Director Shin,
are you back from the conference?
Why did you send so much Korean beef...
(Stock up...)
(Geum Ba Ra)
Hello?
I don't have time for a meal,
but can we meet up for a bit?
I'm on my way.
I like that.
No arguing, no excuses.
There's a nice cafe
in front of the hospital...
Do you know it?
Hi.
What did Yong Joong get you for a gift?
A bracelet.
Why aren't you wearing it?
It doesn't go with my outfit.
I couldn't find anything to buy
under the 600 dollar limit.
It's not like you were on a trip
or anything.
And it makes the receiver
feel awkward, too.
A surgery drained me.
Hey, we're matching today.
See? We're on the same wave.
A whole box of meat...
Are you always this generous?
It will last me for six months.
What are you talking about?
That's a month's worth.
Grill some every day.
Cold hands mean a cold body.
- Any constipation?
- Sometimes?
I make sure to eat enough fiber.
Didn't you miss me?
You did think of me, right?
Yes.
Shouldn't you be heading back in?
Five more minutes.
Don't get sick.
Worried you'll have to come make me
bean sprout soup?
That's nothing too hard.
Are your hands warmer now?
I'll have to grill some
for dinner tonight.
- Alone?
- Should I throw a party?
Medicine doesn't work if you share it.
And don't drink cold things like this.
- You too, Director Shin.
- I'm drinking this to wake myself up.
How long are you going to keep
calling me Director Shin?
It's because you're the director.
Are you one of my patients?
Go on up to the penthouse and wait.
What am I supposed to do there?
You could do a home workout,
or surprise me with a delicious meal.
I'll be done with my rounds around eight.
Since you were so thoughtful to send it,
I'd like to go try some
before I have to freeze it.
Make sure to send me a picture.
Okay.
You didn't eat lunch because of surgery,
did you?
How could I be the only one to eat?
If your mother were still alive,
her heart would break for you.
We all work just to put food
in our mouths.
Does your heart ache for me?
Look at me like that
every once in a while.
I like that look in your eyes.
You should go first.
Why?
We're right in front of the hospital.
Your staff or patients might see us.
So what? What does it matter?
I'm going to get this to go.
I'll think of you every time
I have an Americano.
I'll be thinking of you today, too,
Director Shin.
This is a weird way to put it,
but you were actually kind of cute.
It was a side of you
I never would have imagined.
If I catch a cold,
will you wipe my nose for me too?
Don't work too hard.
- Can I get this to go?
- Sure.
(Momo)
- Yes?
- Did you have to propose to Ba Ra...
and scare her away?
- Scare her away?
- She said she's going abroad.
- When?
- She said goodbye to me yesterday.
- For a trip?
- A trip? I don't think so.
She claims she's going to study,
but that's just what she's saying.
She's leaving to escape you.
What other reason could there be?
I'm hanging up.
(Geum Ba Ra)
Yes, Director Shin.
Can I join you?
I'll cook some for you sometime.
- The meat's no good once it's cold.
- "Sometime"?
Yes.
I'm at your front door.
I came unannounced.
So I can't be mad if you turn me away.
Should I just leave?
Let yourself in.
Where can I wash my hands?
Have a seat.
There's no soup.
It's a stir-fried red pepper paste
made with the sirloin you bought me.
My mom used to make this for me sometimes.
I'll mix it in with my rice.
- Why are you getting up?
- Sesame oil.
No.
I want to taste the red pepper paste.
You didn't mention
you were going on a trip.
I mean, I just saw you a few hours ago.
I was going to email you...
since you're so busy.
And I knew it'd be a long conversation.
Where are you going?
- Is it a secret?
- It's not a secret.
I might move around once I get there.
Does Yong Joong know?
Yes.
My appetite's coming back.
I had no appetite at all before.
- Any wine?
- I don't have any.
Dip it in the sesame oil sauce.
Let's sit here for a bit.
Goodness.
Pickles.
Your mom was glowing.
I suppose it's because
she was proposed to.
What if I die without ever getting
to propose to a woman?
It's embarrassing
getting called a grandfather...
when I'm still a bachelor.
You know the passcode, right?
Have an employee get the leftover meat.
Is Yong Joong paying for your trip?
No.
I worked hard and saved the money myself.
I have enough to last me a few years.
Why are you leaving?
- Just because.
- That's not fair.
Can't you be honest with me?
But you're the one who said
being too honest is rude.
Later...
I'll tell you when I'm ready.
Is there something I don't know?
I'm not ready to talk about it yet.
Momo says it's because of me.
That you feel pressured because of me.
It's not because of you, Director Shin.
What does Yong Joong say?
He doesn't meddle in my affairs.
There's...
someone I like.
That's why I'm leaving.
Who is it?
I'm sorry...
for not telling you sooner.
Show me a picture.
You must have one.
Then I'll believe you.
As a final favor, please don't press me.
I'd rather not say anything right now.
I'll email you once I'm settled in.
And this isn't just an excuse?
For real?
Yes.
Is it Yong Joong?
I knew it.
But why are you leaving?
There's nothing more...
I have to say.
We're just supposed to end it here
like this?
No questions asked?
Although we never started anything...
He told you to just quietly pack up
and leave Korea?
What is it?
Take a deep breath.
Breathe in deeply.
Please, go.
(Nua General Hospital)
Send an ambulance, now.
In front of Jaeil Apartments,
Building 102.
Please...
Just go.
Don't talk.
Want me to give you mouth-to-mouth?
(Doctor Shin)
The numbers are higher than I thought.
Were you okay while I was gone?
(She is eating well.)
Pretend it's champagne and drink it.
Let's set a wedding date.
I hope you like it.
I'm at a loss for words.
- That won't solve anything.
- Hello?
- Yong Joong.
- Yes?
Thank you.
I made a promise to volunteer...
to the Blessed Virgin Mary.
Tell me what you're craving.
My mom always made a full spread
with at least five side dishes.
You're not up for that, are you?
- I'll give it a shot.
- Have you ever seen Ba Ra dance?
No, why?
You don't marry someone out of pity.
It's not pity.
I guess you'll have to make my dress.
- For which embassy party?
- My wedding dress.
Really?
No way!
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)